uberflip.com 2019-07-15

# Legal | Uberflip

## Terms of Use

### Last Updated: June 27, 2019 (superseded Terms of Use dated December 5, 2013)

This service agreement (the “ **Agreement** “) is an agreement between the person or entity visiting, browsing, accessing or otherwise using (the term “use” will refer to any of the foregoing) the Offering (“ **Customer** “) and Flyp Technologies Inc., d/b/a Uberflip with offices at 370 Dufferin St., Toronto, ON M6K 1Z8 (“ **Uberflip** “, together with Customer, the “ **Parties** ” and each, a “ **Party** “), and is entered into as of the earlier of: (A) the date Customer first uses any element of the Offering; and (B) the date Customer agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions set out herein (the “ **Effective Date** “).

BY USING ANY ELEMENT OF THE OFFERING (INCLUDING THE WEBSITE), CUSTOMER ACKNOWLEDGES THAT IT HAS READ, ACCEPTS AND AGREES TO BE BOUND BY AND COMPLY WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET OUT IN THIS AGREEMENT, AS AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME IN ACCORDANCE WITH SECTION 15(K). IF CUSTOMER DOES NOT ACCEPT AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS AGREEMENT, CUSTOMER WILL IMMEDIATELY CEASE ANY FURTHER USE OF THE OFFERING, INCLUDING USE OF ANY ELEMENT THEREOF. CUSTOMER REPRESENTS AND WARRANTS TO UBERFLIP THAT CUSTOMER HAS THE CAPACITY TO ENTER INTO THIS LEGALLY BINDING AGREEMENT. IF CUSTOMER IS USING THE OFFERING ON BEHALF OF ANOTHER PERSON OR ENTITY, CUSTOMER HEREBY REPRESENTS AND WARRANTS TO UBERFLIP THAT CUSTOMER HAS THE AUTHORITY TO BIND SUCH PERSON OR ENTITY TO THIS AGREEMENT.

**1.Definitions**

(a) “ **Agreement** ” has the meaning set out in the introductory paragraph of this Agreement.

(b) “ **Billing Period** ” means the date as set out in the Order Terms or the Website.

(c) “ **Customer Data** ” has the meaning ascribed to it in Section 4(b), and includes Personal Information (if any).

(d) “ **Derivative Data** ” means all modifications, compilations, derivative works and results from processing (including analyses, usage statistics and patterns, datasets, databases, reports, recommendations and visual representations) created or developed from Customer Data or on the basis of Customer’s use of the Services by Uberflip or through the Platform in connection with the Services.

(e) “ **Effective Date** ” has the meaning set out in the introductory paragraph of this Agreement.

(f) “ **Fees** ” means the fees and other charges that apply to Customer’s initial setup and ongoing access to and use of the Services, payable in the amounts and frequency indicated on the Website, in the Order Terms (if applicable) or otherwise communicated by Uberflip to Customer from time to time (including through the Website).

(g) “ **Offering** ” means, collectively, the Platform and the Services.

(h) “ **Order Terms** ” means, if applicable, the order terms provided to Customer which may supplement or modify the terms and conditions set forth herein.

(i) “ **Personal Information** ” means information about an identifiable individual transferred by Customer or its permitted agents to Uberflip hereunder, and any personal information derived or otherwise create by Uberflip in connection therewith.

(j) “ **Platform** ” means, collectively, the Website and all systems of Uberflip and Uberflip’s third-party suppliers that are used in the provision of the Services.

(k) “ **Services** ” means the services to be provided by Uberflip to Customer, as described on the Website, as may be amended or supplemented by Uberflip from time to time in its sole discretion and without notice.

(l) “ **Website** ” means, collectively, the Uberflip websites, including the website located at: http://www.uberflip.com.

(m) “ **Term** ” means the duration of this Agreement.

**2.Services**

(a) Provision of the Services. Uberflip will make the Services available to Customer on the terms and conditions set out in this Agreement and conditional on Customer: (i) making commercially reasonable efforts to cooperate with the reasonable requests of Uberflip; (ii) providing Uberflip with access to any required systems of Customer or third parties (and making all required third-party disclosures and obtaining all required third party consents in respect of such access) which Customer wishes the Platform to obtain data from or provide data to in the course of providing the Services; and (iii) to the extent Customer Data includes Personal Information, providing all notices and disclosures and obtaining all necessary consents and authority in respect of such Personal Information as required under and in compliance with applicable privacy law in order for Uberflip to provide the Services on behalf of Customer and process Personal Information in the manner set out in the Uberflip Privacy Policy.

(b) Provisioning of the Platform. Uberflip will: (i) provide to Customer basic support through the Website as described more fully in Section 8 (Customer Support); and (ii) use commercially reasonable efforts to make the Platform reasonably available with minimal downtime; except for: (A) downtime and scheduled upgrades (as described more fully below); and (B) unavailability caused by circumstances beyond Uberflip’s reasonable control, including acts of God, acts of government, flood, fire, earthquakes, civil unrest, acts of terror, strikes or other labour problems, Internet service provider failures or delays, or the unavailability of any third-party provided goods or services.

(c) Platform Updates and Scheduled Downtime. Uberflip may update the functionality and user interface of the Platform from time to time in its sole discretion as part of its ongoing mission to improve the Offering and the use of the Offering by Uberflip’s other customers. Uberflip may from time to time schedule downtime for maintenance and upgrades without prior notice.

(d) No Responsibility for Data Storage and Backup. Uberflip cannot guarantee that the Platform will provide regular data backups of any Customer Data stored on it. It is Customer’s responsibility to backup onto Customer’s own local system all Customer Data, including all data, files and records that Customer submits to Uberflip.

**3\. License Grants.**

(a) License Grants by Uberflip. Subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement and Customer’s compliance therewith, Uberflip grants to Customer: (i) a revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable license during the Term to access and use the Platform over the Internet and through the then available standard interface for the Platform in connection with receiving the Services in accordance with this Agreement; and (ii) a revocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, non-transferable license to copy, use, reproduce and modify any Derivative Data provided to Customer for Customer’s internal business purposes only.

(b) License Grant by Customer. Subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement, including Uberflip’s confidentiality obligations, Customer grants to Uberflip a transferrable, sublicenseable, royalty-free, fully paid-up, worldwide license to copy, use, reproduce, modify, develop, access, collect and store the Customer Data solely for the purpose of providing the Services.

**4\. Reservation of Rights.**

(a) Rights Reserved by Uberflip. Uberflip expressly reserves all rights in the Services, the Platform, all Derivative Data and all materials (other than Personal Information) provided by Uberflip hereunder and not specifically granted to Customer (“Uberflip Property”). All right, title and interest in the Uberflip Property, as well as any update, modification, adaptation, translation, customization or derivative work thereof, and all intellectual property rights therein will remain with Uberflip (or Uberflip’s third party suppliers, as applicable). The Uberflip Property is licensed on a subscription basis on the terms and conditions of this Agreement and not “sold” to Customer.

(b) Rights Reserved by Customer. Customer expressly reserves all rights in any data, information, records and files that Customer (or any User) loads, transmits to or enters into the Platform, including data that the Platform is configured to obtain from Customer’s servers or systems or from third parties on Customer’s behalf, but excluding any Derivative Data (the “Customer Data”), subject to the license that Customer grants Uberflip in accordance with the provisions of this Agreement, and provided that Customer does not acquire any intellectual property rights in the Services, the Platform, any Derivative Data or any elements of any of the foregoing.

**5\. Privacy Policy; Internet Security Disclaimer; Limitation, Suspension or Termination of Access.**

(a) Privacy Policy. To the extent that Customer Data may contain any Personal Information, Uberflip will collect, use, disclose such Personal Information for the purposes authorized under this Agreement and in accordance with Uberflip’ privacy policy located at: www.uberflip.com/privacy (the “ **Privacy Policy** “). The Privacy Policy is hereby incorporated by reference and forms part of this Agreement.

(b) Internet Security Disclaimer. As between Uberflip and Customer, Customer is solely responsible for the accuracy, quality, integrity, legality, reliability, and appropriateness of all Customer Data. Customer understands that the technical processing and transmission Customer Data is fundamentally necessary to use of the Services. Therefore, Customer expressly consents to Uberflip’s storage of Customer Data, which will involve transmission over the Internet, and over various networks, only part of which may be owned and/or operated by Uberflip. Uberflip will endeavor to provide industry-standard secure data transmission channels for use by Customer to upload, enter or transmit Customer Data to the Services, for example through the use of the HTTPS protocol. However, despite such efforts, Customer acknowledges and understands that Customer Data may be accessed by unauthorized persons when communicated across the Internet, network communications facilities, telephone or other electronic means. Uberflip is not responsible for any Customer Data which is delayed, lost, altered, intercepted or stored during the transmission of any data whatsoever across public networks not owned or operated by Uberflip, including, the Internet, third party websites, and Customer’s local network. Customer agrees that Uberflip is not in any way responsible for any interference with Customer’s use of or access to the Services or security breaches arising from or attributable to the Internet, and Customer waives any and all claims against Uberflip in connection therewith.

(c) Limitation, Suspension or Termination of Access. In addition to any other suspension or termination rights of Uberflip pursuant to this Agreement, certain extraordinary circumstances may require Uberflip to suspend, terminate or limit (as appropriate and as determined in Uberflip’s sole discretion) Customer’s access to or use of the Platform or the Services, or any component thereof, without notice in order to: (i) prevent any misuse or abuse of the Offering or other Uberflip Property; (ii) prevent any damage to, or degradation of the integrity of Uberflip’s systems or Uberflip Property; (iii) comply with any law, regulation, court order, or other governmental request or order; or (iv) otherwise protect Uberflip from potential legal liability or harm to its reputation or business. Uberflip also reserves the right to approve, reject, cancel or remove any Customer Data or other content that is posted on, provided or uploaded to, or transmitted through the Platform or the Services at any time and for any reason in Uberflip’s sole discretion, and Uberflip will not be liable or responsible for exercising this right. For greater clarity, Customer acknowledges and agrees that Uberflip does not guarantee that any Customer Data or other content that is posted on, provided or uploaded to, or transmitted through the Platform or the Services will be available or displayed. Uberflip will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify Customer of the reasons for such limitation, suspension or termination action as soon as reasonably practicable. In the event of a limitation or suspension, Uberflip will promptly restore Customer’s access to the Offering as soon as the event giving rise to the limitation or suspension has been resolved, as determined in Uberflip’s sole discretion. Nothing contained in this Agreement will be construed so as to limit Uberflip’s ability to take action or invoke remedies, or act as a waiver of Uberflip’s rights in any way with respect to any of the foregoing activities. Uberflip will not be responsible for any loss or damages incurred by Customer as a result of any limitation, termination or suspension of access to or use of the Platform or the Services under this Section.

**6\. Customer Responsibilities and Restrictions.**

(a) Customer ID. Upon Customer’s request, but subject to any applicable limitations associated with Customer’s subscription, Uberflip will issue user identification and password (“User ID”) to Customer for each individual Customer wishes to have access to and use of the Offering (each, a “User”). Customer may only identify its partners, shareholders, employees and contractors who, in each case, are bound by confidentiality restrictions at least as restrictive as this Agreement as Users. Users may only access and use the Platform and the Services through a User ID issued to Customer. Customer will not allow Users to share their User ID with any other person. Customer is responsible for any and all activity occurring under the User IDs associated with Users. Customer is responsible for all use of the Offering by Users and for maintaining the confidentiality of their User ID and will promptly notify Uberflip of any actual or suspected unauthorized use of the Offering. Uberflip reserves the right to replace any User ID if it determines it may have been used for an unauthorized purpose.

(b) Customer Responsibilities and Restrictions. Customer agrees that Customer is responsible for the compliance by the Users with this Agreement and for the Users’ use of the Offering, as well as for ensuring that the Users maintain the confidentiality of their User IDs. Customer agrees that Customer is responsible for all charges incurred by the Users in connection with access to or use of the Offering and generally for any activity occurring through a User ID. Without limiting the generality of any of the foregoing, Customer agrees that Customer will not, and will not permit any person to:

(i) use the Offering other than as permitted by this Agreement;

(ii) use the Offering to send, store, publish, post, upload or otherwise transmit any Customer Data in violation of any warranty, representation or obligation of Customer under this Agreement;

(iii) license, sublicense, sell, resell, rent, lease, transfer, assign, distribute, time share or otherwise commercially exploit or make the Offering (in whole or in part) available to any third party, other than to the Users, or as otherwise expressly contemplated in accordance with this Agreement;

(iv) use the Offering to upload, collect, transmit, store, use or process, or ask Uberflip to obtain from third parties, any Customer Data: (A) that Customer does not have the lawful right to copy, transmit, distribute, and display (including any Customer Data that would violate any confidentiality or fiduciary obligations that Customer might have with respect to the Customer Data); (B) for which Customer does not have the authority, consent or permission from the individual(s) to whom the Personal Information relates in accordance with applicable privacy legislation; (C) that infringes, misappropriates or otherwise violates any intellectual property or other proprietary rights of any third party (including any copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, or other intellectual property right, or moral right or right of publicity); (D) that is tortious, defamatory, obscene, or offensive; or (E) that violates, or encourages any conduct that would violate, any applicable law or regulation (including applicable privacy and anti-spam legislation) or would give rise to civil or criminal liability.

(v) use the Offering to send, store, publish, post, upload or otherwise transmit any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, corrupted files or other computer programming routines that are intended to damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any systems, data, personal information or property of another;

(vi) continue to use the Offering in a manner that interferes with or disrupts the integrity or performance of the Offering following a notice from Uberflip of such use;

(vii) attempt to gain unauthorized access to the Offering or its related systems or networks;

(viii) use or knowingly permit the use of any security testing tools in order to probe, scan or attempt to penetrate or ascertain the security of the Offering;

(ix) use any data mining, robots or similar data gathering or extraction methods (including electronic address harvesting);

(x) access the Offering for the purpose of building a similar or competitive product or service or for the purpose of obtaining unauthorized access to the Offering; or

(xi) copy, translate, create a derivative work of, reverse engineer, reverse assemble, disassemble, or decompile the Offering or any part thereof or otherwise attempt to discover any source code or modify the Offering, except as expressly provided for in this Agreement.

(c) Customer Responsibility for Customer Data. Customer has sole responsibility for providing all notices, making all disclosures and otherwise obtaining all necessary consent and authority required by and in accordance with applicable laws regarding Customer Data (including any Personal Information). Uberflip will use the Customer Data it is provided by Customer or third parties in performing the Services “as is”, and is not responsible for reviewing, validating or otherwise confirming the accuracy, appropriateness or completeness of Customer Data.

(d) Removal of Customer Data on Request by Customer. Customer may control the Customer Data stored by the Services, including (subject to Section 10(b)) by deleting or requiring Uberflip to delete all or part of the Customer Data (including Personal Information) at any time.

**7\. Term.**

This Agreement will commence on the Effective Date and continue in effect until terminated in accordance with its terms, or as otherwise set out in the Order Terms.

**8\. Customer Support.**

Uberflip will provide the following support to Customer:

(a) Web and Email Support. Customer will have access to Uberflip’s technical support part of the Website and may use the available interfaces, including any customer support email addresses posted thereon, to submit service requests.

(b) Incident Management. Uberflip will use commercially reasonable efforts to correct any reproducible failure of the Offering to substantially conform to its expected operation; provided that Uberflip will not have an obligation to provide a correction for all such nonconformities.

**9\. Fees and Payment.**

(a) Fees. Customer will pay to Uberflip the Fees in the manner, amounts and frequencies indicated on the Website, in the Order Terms (if applicable) or otherwise communicated by Uberflip to Customer from time to time (including through the Website).

(b) Payment. Unless otherwise indicated on the Website or, if applicable, the Order Terms: (i) Fees are payable in advance on or after the first day of the applicable billing period; and (ii) if required by Uberflip, Customer will provide to Uberflip (and keep current at all times during the Term) the details (including number, date of expiry and CVC) of a valid credit card that is acceptable to Uberflip in its sole discretion (the “Credit Card”). Customer hereby agrees and authorizes Uberflip to charge the Credit Card for any Fees that become due and payable hereunder. Any Fees in respect of non-recurring or one-time charges incurred during a billing period will be automatically charged to the Credit Card on or after the first day of the next billing period. One time fees (including any fees for add ons) are charged at the time in which the Applicable Agreement is approved. In the event the Billing Start Date set out in the Order Terms is a date that is not the first day of the calendar month, Uberflip may pro-rate the applicable Fees based on the number of days in the first Billing Period of the Term and thereafter adjust the payments to recur on the first day of the calendar month for each of the remaining billing periods during the Term. If the Term ends on any day other than the date that is not the last day of the calendar month, Uberflip may pro-rate the applicable Fees based on the number of days in the last billing period of the Term. If applicable, any Fees paid in advance will be applied against monthly invoices on the first day of each calendar month of the Term.

(c) Invoices. From time to time, Uberflip may prepare and send to Customer, at the then-current contact information on file with Uberflip, invoices for any Fees and other amounts that have become due and payable under this Agreement. Unless otherwise expressly stipulated in an invoice, Customer agrees to pay all invoiced amounts immediately upon receipt.

(d) No Set-Off and Late Payment Charge. Customer may not withhold or “set-off” any amounts due under this Agreement. Unless otherwise indicated on the Website, all Fees are non-refundable and Uberflip will provide no full or partial credits or refunds, including in respect of Services that are paid for but not used by Customer. Uberflip reserves the right to suspend Customer’s access to the Offering until all due amounts are paid in full. Any late payment will be increased by the costs of collection (including reasonable legal fees), and will incur interest at the rate of one and a half percent (1.5%) compounded monthly (19.56% annually), or the maximum legal rate (if less) per month or fraction thereof until fully paid.

(e) Certain Taxes. Fees and charges quoted in this Agreement do not include, and Customer will pay, indemnify and hold Uberflip harmless, from all sales, use, gross receipts, value-added, GST/HST, personal property or other taxes, and all applicable duties, tariffs, assessments, export and import fees or similar charges (including interest and penalties imposed thereon) on the transactions contemplated in connection with this Agreement, other than taxes based on the net income or profits of Uberflip.

**10\. Confidential & Proprietary Information.**

(a) Definitions. For purposes of this section, a Party receiving Confidential & Proprietary Information (as defined below) will be the “ **Recipient** ” and the Party disclosing such information will be the “ **Discloser** “, and “ **Confidential & Proprietary Information**” includes all information disclosed by Discloser to Recipient during the Term of this Agreement and marked as “confidential” or “proprietary” or which a reasonable person would understand to be confidential or proprietary; provided that: (a) the terms and conditions of this Agreement, all Derivative Data and all parts of the Offering, whether marked as “confidential” or “proprietary” or not, will be considered to be Uberflip Confidential & Proprietary Information; and (b) all Customer Data (but excluding any Derivative Data), whether marked as “confidential” or “proprietary” or not, will be considered Customer’s Confidential & Proprietary Information; and further provided that Discloser’s Confidential & Proprietary Information (other than Personal Information) does not include: (i) information already known or independently developed by Recipient outside the scope of this relationship by personnel not having access to any Discloser’s Confidential & Proprietary Information; (ii) information that is publicly available through no wrongful act of Recipient; or (iii) information received by Recipient from a third party who was free to disclose it without confidentiality obligations.

(b) Covenant. Recipient hereby agrees that during the Term and at all times thereafter it will not: (i) disclose such Confidential & Proprietary Information of the Discloser to any person or entity, except to its own personnel, affiliates or contractors having a “need to know”, and to such other recipients as the Discloser may approve in writing; (ii) use Confidential & Proprietary Information of the Discloser except to exercise its license rights or perform its obligations under this Agreement; or (iii) alter or remove from any Confidential & Proprietary Information of the Discloser any proprietary legend. Recipient will use at least the same degree of care in safeguarding the Confidential & Proprietary Information of the Discloser as it uses in safeguarding its own confidential information of a similar nature, but in no event will less than due diligence and reasonable care be exercised. Each party will be deemed to have fulfilled its confidentiality obligations under this Section 10, if it affords the other party’s Confidential & Proprietary Information at least the same degree of care it takes in protecting its own confidential information from unauthorized disclosure (but in no event using less than a reasonable degree of care). Upon the earlier of: (A) Discloser’s written request; and (B) the termination or expiration of this Agreement, regardless of whether a dispute may exist, Recipient will return or destroy (as instructed by Discloser) all Confidential & Proprietary Information of Discloser in its possession or control and cease all further use thereof. Uberflip may retain a copy of such Confidential & Proprietary Information for the sole purpose of and to the extent necessary for it to comply with applicable and legal, regulatory, or reasonable internal back-up or archival policies and requirements. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Recipient may disclose Discloser’s Confidential & Proprietary Information to the extent that such disclosure is necessary for the Recipient to enforce its rights under this Agreement or is required by law or by the order of a court or similar judicial or administrative body, provided that the Recipient promptly notifies the Discloser in writing of such required disclosure and cooperates with the Discloser to seek an appropriate protective order.

(c) Injunctive Relief. Recipient acknowledges that violation of the provisions of this section would cause irreparable harm to Discloser not adequately compensable by monetary damages. In addition to other relief, it is agreed that injunctive relief will be available without necessity of posting bond to prevent any actual or threatened violation of such provisions.

**11\. Customer Warranty; Disclaimer; Indemnity.**

(a) Customer Warranty. Customer represents and warrants to, and covenants with Uberflip that: (i) the Customer Data will contain no information about an identifiable individual or information that is otherwise subject to privacy laws (“ **Personal Information** “), except for Personal Information: (A) in respect of which Customer has provided all notices and disclosures and otherwise obtained all necessary consents and authority from all applicable individuals in accordance with applicable laws to enable Uberflip to provide the Services on behalf of Customer and to process Personal Information in the manner set out in the Uberflip Privacy Policy; and (B) that complies with Customer’s representations, warranties and obligations set out in this Agreement; and (ii) Customer will agree to and at all times comply with (and will cause each User to agree to and at all times comply with) all third-party terms and conditions applicable in respect of the Offering.

(b) Disclaimer. THE OFFERING AND ANY OTHER PRODUCTS AND SERVICES PROVIDED BY UBERFLIP TO CUSTOMER ARE PROVIDED “AS IS”, “AS AVAILABLE”, WITH ALL FAULTS AND WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND. UBERFLIP HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL EXPRESS, IMPLIED, COLLATERAL OR STATUTORY WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR CONDITIONS, WHETHER WRITTEN OR ORAL, INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, TITLE, NONINFRINGEMENT, SECURITY, RELIABILITY, COMPLETENESS, QUIET ENJOYMENT, ACCURACY, QUALITY, INTEGRATION OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. UBERFLIP DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE OFFERING WILL OPERATE WITHOUT INTERRUPTION OR BE ERROR FREE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF ANY OF THE FOREGOING, UBERFLIP EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY THAT ANY DATA OR INFORMATION PROVIDED TO CUSTOMER IN CONNECTION WITH CUSTOMER’S USE OF THE OFFERING WILL BE ACCURATE, OR CAN OR SHOULD BE RELIED UPON BY CUSTOMER FOR ANY PURPOSE WHATSOEVER.

(c) Indemnity. Customer agrees to indemnify and hold harmless Uberflip, its employees, officers, directors and affiliates against any and all liability (including losses, damages, recoveries, deficiencies, interest, penalties and reasonable attorney’s fees) relating to: (i) Customer Data, (ii) Customer’s breach of any of Customer’s obligations, representations or warranties under this Agreement; or (iii) Customer’s use of the Offering, including in combination with any third party software, application or service.

**12\. Limitation of Liabilities.**

The Parties acknowledge that the following provisions have been negotiated by them and reflect a fair allocation of risk and form an essential basis of the bargain and will survive and continue in full force and effect despite any failure of consideration or of an exclusive remedy:

(a) Amount. IN NO EVENT WILL THE TOTAL AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF UBERFLIP IN CONNECTION WITH OR UNDER THIS AGREEMENT EXCEED THE TOTAL AMOUNT OF FEES RECEIVED BY UBERFLIP UNDER THIS AGREEMENT DURING THE PRECEDING 12 MONTHS. FOR GREATER CERTAINTY, THE EXISTENCE OF ONE OR MORE CLAIMS UNDER THIS AGREEMENT WILL NOT INCREASE THIS MAXIMUM LIABILITY AMOUNT. IN NO EVENT WILL UBERFLIP’S SUPPLIERS HAVE ANY LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED TO THIS AGREEMENT.

(b) Type. IN NO EVENT WILL UBERFLIP BE LIABLE TO CUSTOMER FOR ANY: (I) SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES; (II) LOST SAVINGS, PROFIT, DATA, USE OR GOODWILL; (III) BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, EVEN IF NOTIFIED IN ADVANCE OF SUCH POSSIBILITY; OR (IV) PERSONAL OR PROPERTY DAMAGE ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED TO THIS AGREEMENT, REGARDLESS OF CAUSE OF ACTION OR THE THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE, GROSS NEGLIGENCE, FUNDAMENTAL BREACH, BREACH OF A FUNDAMENTAL TERM) OR OTHERWISE. IN NO EVENT WILL UBERFLIP BE LIABLE FOR PROCUREMENT OR COSTS OF SUBSTITUTE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES.

**13\. Notices.**

Notices sent to either Party will be effective when delivered in person or by email, one day after being sent by overnight courier, or two days after being sent by first class mail postage prepaid to the official contact designated by the Parties and immediately after being received by the other party’s server. Notices must be in writing and sent: (a) if to Uberflip, to the address set out in the introductory paragraph of this Agreement; and (b) if to Customer, to the current postal or email address that Uberflip has on file with respect to Customer. Uberflip may change its contact information by posting the new contact information on the Website or by giving notice thereof to Customer. Customer is solely responsible for keeping its contact information on file with Uberflip current at all times during the Term.

**14\. Termination.**

(a) Generally. Either Party may, in addition to other relief, suspend or terminate this Agreement if the other Party: (i) commits a material breach of this Agreement, and either: (A) fails within seven days after receipt of notice of such breach to correct such material breach or to commence corrective action reasonably acceptable to the aggrieved Party and proceed with due diligence to completion; or (B) such material breach is incapable of being cured; or (B) becomes insolvent, makes an assignment for the benefit of its creditors, a receiver is appointed, or a petition in bankruptcy is filed with respect to the Party and is not dismissed within 30 days.

(b) Survival. Upon termination or expiration of this Agreement for any reason: (a) all rights and obligations of both Parties (except for Customer’s payment of all Fees and other amounts then owing in accordance herewith), including all licenses granted hereunder, will immediately terminate except as provided below; (b) within 30 days after the effective date of termination, each Party will comply with the obligations to return or destroy all Confidential Information of the other Party, as set forth Section 10 (Confidential & Proprietary Information). The following Sections will survive expiration or termination of this Agreement for any reason: Section 4 (Reservation of Rights), Section 6 (Customer Responsibilities and Restrictions), Section 10 (Confidential & Proprietary Information), Section 11 (Customer Warranty; Disclaimer; Indemnity), Section 12 (Limitation of Liabilities), Section 14(b) (Survival), and Section 15 (General Provisions).

**15\. General Provisions.**

(a) Assignment. Customer may not assign this Agreement to any third party without Uberflip’s prior written consent, except that Customer may assign its rights (but not obligations) hereunder to an affiliate of Customer. Uberflip may assign this Agreement, in whole or in part, to any third party without Customer’s consent. Any assignment in violation of this Section will be void. The terms of this Agreement will be binding upon and inure to the benefit of the Parties’ successors and permitted assignees.

(b) Choice of Law. This Agreement and any action related thereto will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Province of Ontario and the federal laws of Canada applicable therein, without regard to conflicts of law principles. The Parties hereby irrevocably attorn to the exclusive personal jurisdiction and venue of the courts sitting in Toronto, Ontario. The U.N. Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods will not apply to this Agreement.

(c) Right to List as a Customer. Customer agrees that Uberflip may utilize Customer’s name in listings of current customers. Use of Customer’s name in any other marketing materials or press announcements will be submitted to Customer in advance for approval, provided that such approval will not be unreasonably withheld.

(d) Compliance with Export Regulations. Customer has or will obtain in a timely manner all necessary or appropriate licenses, permits or other governmental authorizations or approvals; will indemnify and hold Uberflip harmless from, and bear all expense of, complying with all foreign or domestic laws, regulations or requirements pertaining to the importation, exportation, or use of the Offering. Customer will not directly or indirectly export or re-export (including by transmission) any regulated technology to any country to which such activity is restricted by regulation or statute, without the prior written consent, if required, of the administrator of export laws.

(e) Construction. Except as otherwise provided herein, the Parties rights and remedies under this Agreement are cumulative. The term “including” means “including without limitation.” The headings of sections of this Agreement are for reference purposes only and have no substantive effect. The terms “consent” or “discretion”, when used in respect of Uberflip herein mean the right of Uberflip to withhold such consent or exercise such discretion (as applicable) arbitrarily and without any implied obligation to act reasonably or explain its decision to Customer. Unless otherwise indicated, all dollar amounts are in United States Dollars.

(f) Force Majeure. Neither Party will be liable for delays caused by events beyond its reasonable control, except non-payment of amounts due hereunder will not be excused by this provision.

(g) Severable. Any provision hereof found by a tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be illegal or unenforceable will be automatically conformed to the minimum requirements of law and all other provisions will remain in full force and effect.

(h) No Waiver. Waiver of any provision hereof in one instance will not preclude enforcement thereof on future occasions. Any waiver by one Party of any default by the other Party will not affect or impair any rights of the first Party arising from any subsequent default by that other Party.

(i) Independent Contractors. Customer’s relationship to Uberflip is that of an independent contractor, and neither Party is an agent or partner of the other. Customer will not have, and will not represent to any third party that it has, any authority to act on behalf of Uberflip.

(j) Entire Agreement. This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the Parties with respect to the subject matter hereof and supersedes all other communications, whether written or oral. This Agreement may be executed in one or more counterparts, each of which will be deemed an original and all of which will be taken together and deemed to be one instrument.

(k) Amendments. Subject to the following sentence, no amendment, supplement, modification, waiver or termination of this Agreement and, unless otherwise specified, no consent or approval by any Party, will be binding unless executed in writing by the Party or Parties to be bound thereby. NOTWITHSTANDING THE PRECEDING SENTENCE, UBERFLIP MAY UNILATERALLY AMEND THIS AGREEMENT, IN WHOLE OR IN PART (EACH, AN “ **AMENDMENT** “), BY: (I) GIVING CUSTOMER PRIOR NOTICE OF SUCH AMENDMENT; OR (II) POSTING NOTICE OF SUCH AMENDMENT ON THE WEBSITE. UNLESS OTHERWISE INDICATED BY UBERFLIP, ANY SUCH AMENDMENT WILL BECOME EFFECTIVE AS OF THE DATE NOTICE THEREOF IS PROVIDED TO CUSTOMER OR IS POSTED ON THE WEBSITE (WHICHEVER IS EARLIER).

(l) English Language. It is the express wish of the parties that this Agreement and all related documents be drawn up in English. C’est la volonté expresse des parties que la présente convention ainsi que les documents qui s’y rattachent soient rédigés en anglais.

## Copyright Policy

### Last Updated: September 5, 2013

Uberflip does not permit copyright infringing activities and infringement of intellectual property rights through the use of its services and reserves the right to remove any content that breaches its content policy (including materials which are obscene, pornographic, profane, harmful to minors or otherwise objectionable in Uberflip’s reasonable view). In addition, Uberflip reserves the right, if properly notified that content infringes on another’s intellectual property rights, to remove such content. If a copyright owner or an agent thereof contacts Uberflip regarding any content and claiming that its use through the Uberflip services infringes upon copyright, Uberflip will require the following information from the person claiming copyright infringement or that person’s agent (the “ **Complainant** “):

  * an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the Complainant if they are the owner of the copyright’s interest;
  * a description of the copyrighted work that Complainant claims has been infringed, including the URL (i.e., web page address) of the location where the copyrighted work exists or a copy of the copyrighted work;
  * identification of the URL or other specific location where the material that Complainant claims is infringing is located; contact information from the Complainant;
  * a statement by Complainant that Complainant has a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
  * a statement by Complainant, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in his/her notice is accurate and that Complainant is the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.

## Cookie Policy

### Last Updated: May 3, 2019

Our websites use cookies and other tracking technologies to give you the best browsing experience. You can find out more on cookies and how we use them below. For further information on the processing of your personal data by Flyp Technologies Inc., please read our Privacy Policy.

**Essential Website Cookies**

These cookies are strictly necessary for the websites to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the websites, you cannot refuse them without impacting how our websites function. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.

Domain(s) | Cookie(s)  
---|---  
uberflip.com | 

  * uf_privacy_prefs
  * _MGZ_
  * OptanonConsent
  * OptanonAlertBoxClosed

**Performance and Functionality Cookies**

These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of our websites, but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality may become unavailable.

Domain(s) | Cookie(s)  
---|---  
uberflip.com | 

  * pdf_event
  * ei_client_id
  * s-9da4
  * _biz_flagsA
  * __distillery
  * ufentry
  * __hssc
  * __hssrc
  * _gid
  * __hstc
  * _hjIncludedInSample
  * ubvt
  * _ufav
  * _ufas

hs-analytics.net | 

  * __cfduid

wistia.net | 

  * wistia-top-domain-getter

fast.wistia.com | 

  * wistia-http2-push-disabled

fast.wistia.net | 

  * __distillery
  * wistia-http2-push-disabled

**Analytics and Personalization Cookies**

These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our websites are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us personalize our websites and platform for you in order to enhance your experience.

Domain(s) | Cookie(s)  
---|---  
uberflip.com | 

  * _biz_sid
  * _biz_uid
  * _biz_dfsA
  * d-a8e6
  * trwv.uid
  * wistia-top-domain-getter
  * trwsa.sid
  * _gat_UA48039851
  * _biz_nA
  * _biz_pendingA
  * _ga
  * optimizelyPendingLogEvents
  * optimizelyEndUserId
  * optimizelyBuckets
  * optimizelySegments
  * _mkto_trk
  * _gat_UA-nnnnnnn-nn
  * _gat
  * __atuvc
  * __atuvs
  * hubspotutk

bizible.com | 

  * _BUID

hs-scripts.com | 

  * __cfduid

in.ml314.com | 

  * AWSELB

abrtp1.marketo.com | 

  * BIGipServerabrtp1_https

hubspot.com | 

  * __cfduid

abrtp1-cdn.marketo.com | 

  * BIGipServerabrtp1_https

analytics.twitter.com | 

  * lang

**Advertising and Targeting Cookies**

These cookies are used to make advertising messages more relevant to you and your interests. They also perform functions like preventing the same ad from continuously reappearing, ensuring that ads are properly displayed, and in some cases selecting advertisements that are based on your interests. They do not store directly personal information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.

Domain(s) | Cookie(s)  
---|---  
ps.eyeota.net | 

  * ONPLFTRH

facebook.com | 

  * datr
  * fr
  * lu

youtube.com | 

  * SID
  * HSID
  * demographics
  * VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
  * PREF
  * APISID
  * GPS
  * SSID
  * LOGIN_INFO
  * YSC
  * SAPISID

lijit.com | 

  * ljt_reader

jivox.com | 

  * jvxsync
  * jvxbksync

tapad.com | 

  * TapAd_DID
  * TapAd_TS

analytics.twitter.com | 

  * lang

crwdcntrl.net | 

  * _cc_cc
  * _cc_id
  * _cc_aud
  * _cc_dc

addthis.com | 

  * ouid
  * loc
  * xtc
  * bku
  * mus
  * uid
  * uvc
  * di2
  * vc

ads.linkedin.com | 

  * BizoID
  * UserMatchHistory
  * lang

tribalfusion.com | 

  * ANON_ID

linkedin.com | 

  * lidc
  * bcookie
  * __utma
  * __utmv
  * bscookie
  * __qca
  * visit

twitter.com | 

  * auth_token
  * twll
  * secure_session
  * guest_id
  * __utma
  * personalization_id
  * remember_checked
  * remember_checked_on

google.com | 

  * APISID
  * SSID
  * PREF
  * SID
  * SAPISID
  * HSID

bluekai.com | 

  * bku
  * bkdc

ml314.com | 

  * u
  * tp
  * pi

prfct.co | 

  * pa_openx_ts
  * pa_twitter_ts
  * pa_google_ts
  * pa_yahoo_ts
  * pa_mrin_ts
  * pa_rubicon_ts
  * pa_uid

adnxs.com | 

  * anj
  * uuid2

pinterest.com | 

  * __utma
  * _pinterest_sess
  * __utmv

demdex.net | 

  * demdex

dpm.demdex.net | 

  * dpm

rlcdn.com | 

  * rtn1-z
  * drtn1609000981
  * ck1
  * rlas3

semasio.net | 

  * SEUNCY

mathtag.com | 

  * uuidc
  * uuid

openx.net | 

  * i

taboola.com | 

  * t_gid
  * taboola_usg

doubleclick.net | 

  * id

## Anti-Spam Policy

Uberflip has a no tolerance spam policy. Uberflip’s customer support actively monitors large import lists and emails going to a large number of contacts. Any customer found to be using Uberflip for spam will be immediately cut-off from use of the product. If you know of or suspect any violators, please notify us immediately at support.

Every email contains a mandatory unsubscribe link – those individuals who try to remove this link will be warned that they are doing so. If the link is removed or de-activated in any way, Uberflip will terminate the customer’s account.

**What is Spam?**

Spam is unsolicited email also known as UCE (Unsolicited Commercial Email). By sending email to only to those who have requested to receive it, you are following accepted permission-based email guidelines.

**What constitutes a Preexisting business relationship?**

The recipient of your email has made a purchase, requested information, responded to a questionnaire or a survey, or had offline contact with you.

**How Uberflip protects you from sending spam:**

Uberflip’s Subscription Management E-Delivery Tool is a permission-based email-marketing tool that follows the strictest permission-based philosophies:

  * **Communication** – Your Uberflip registration page already states why you are collecting the site visitor’s email address, how you plan to use their address, and that you are following the embedded privacy policy. Additionally, by accepting our license agreement you have agreed to use only permission-based lists and never to sell or rent your lists.
  * **Verification** – Uberflip automatically sends all of your new contacts an email confirming their interest in receiving emails from you.
  * **Unsubscribe** – Every email generated from Uberflip contains an unsubscribe link which allows your contacts to opt-out of future emails and automatically updates your contact lists to avoid the chance of sending unwanted emails to visitors who have unsubscribed.
  * **Identification** – Your email header information is correct because it is pre-set for you by Uberflip. Your email’s “From” address is verified and already accurately identifies you as the sender.

**What constitutes consent?**

The recipient of your email has been clearly and fully notified of the collection and use of his email address and has consented prior to such collection and use. This is often called informed consent.

**Isn’t there a law against sending Spam?**

The federal anti-spam law went into effect on January 1st, 2004 and preempts all state laws. While this new law will not stop spam, it does make most spam illegal and ultimately less attractive to spammers. The law is specific about requirements to send commercial email and empowers the federal government to enforce the law. The penalties can include a fine and/or imprisonment for up to 5 years.

**How to protect yourself from Spam: Take the Spam Test**

  * Are you importing a purchased list of ANY kind?
  * Are you sending to non-specific addresses such as:  
sales@domain.com, business@domain.com, webmaster@domain.com, info@domain.com, or other general addresses.
  * Are you sending to distribution lists or mailing lists which send indirectly to a variety of email addresses?
  * Are you mailing to anyone who has not explicitly agreed to join your mailing list?
  * Have you falsified your originating address or transmission path information?
  * Have you used a third party email address or domain name without their permission?
  * Does your email’s subject line contain false or misleading information?
  * Does your email fail to provide a working link to unsubscribe?
  * Are you failing to process any unsubscribe requests that come to you via a reply to your email within 10 days or the request?

If you have answered YES to ANY of the above questions you will likely be labeled a SPAMMER. For more information visit The Coalition Against Unsolicited Email ([www.cauce.org](http://www.cauce.org/)) or contact Uberflip Customer Support ([support@uberflip.com](mailto:support@uberflip.com)).

## Data Processing Amendment (DPA)

### Last Updated: April 2, 2019

Please contact [dpo@uberflip.com](mailto:dpo@uberflip.com) if your organization is established in the European Union (EU) or subject to the GDPR and requires a DPA. Please click here to download our DPA for your review.

## Privacy Policy

### Last Updated: May 23, 2018 (superseded Privacy Policy dated July 6, 2015)

Flyp Technologies Inc. d/b/a Uberflip (“Uberflip”, “we”, “us”, “our”) is committed to the protection of the personal information. As part of this commitment, we have set out this Privacy Policy to describe the manner in which we treat the personal information that we maintain on behalf of our customers (“Customers”), as well as the personal information we collect, such as through our website at [www.uberflip.com](http://uberflip.com/) (“Website”).

**Collection & Use of Information**

_Information we maintain on behalf of our Customers_

Uberflip helps marketers and other Customers create, manage and optimize the content experience on their websites by aggregating existing content (blogs, social media, eBooks, videos and more) into an online content hub (“Hub”), and also provides other content management solutions to Customers (collectively, the “Services”).

Our Customers choose what information to collect or make available through the Services we provide on their behalf, and the Customer’s end users interacting with the content or Services (“Audience Members”) may upload or post information to the Services (collectively, “User Content”). Depending on the Customer, User Content may contain personal information. We receive and maintain this information on behalf of our Customers in order to provide the Services, and we do not use such information for any other purpose except as set out herein or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable law. We rely on our Customers to comply with applicable privacy and related laws when collecting, using or disclosing personal information in connection with the Services.

If you signed-up to receive marketing communications from one of our Customers and now wish to unsubscribe, please contact the Customer directly as we are not responsible for the sending of such communications.

To learn more about information we maintain on behalf of Customers, see also the sections entitled “Website Data and Analytics” and “Online Advertising” below.

_Information we collect and use_

  * Some of our Services require you to create an account. If you create an account, we collect information such as name, company name and contact information (including email address, mailing address, telephone number), payment card information, as well as a user name and password that you provide. We use this information in order to provide the Services you request and to process payments. We may also use this information to offer you tailored content within some of our Services.
  * If you sign-up for a free trial, demo, event, webinar or other offer, we may collect your name, job title, and business contact information (including email address, phone number) and certain information about your company. We use this information to contact you and otherwise facilitate or provide you with your offer.
  * If you sign-up to receive marketing communications from Uberflip, we collect your name and email address in order to send you mail or e-mail regarding products and services that we believe are of interest to you. Similarly, if you subscribe to receive email notifications regarding a discussion on our Website, we collect your email address in order to send you the notifications you request. You may also be added to our marketing list when you create an Uberflip account. If you do not want to continue to receive such marketing and promotional communications from us, you may “opt-out” at any time by using the unsubscribe mechanism in any of our emails or by contacting us as set out under “Contact Us” below <http://mktg.uberflip.com/email-preferences.html>). Please note that you may continue certain transactional and account-related messages from us.
  * If you apply for a job at Uberflip, you may provide us with certain personal information about yourself (such as that contained in a resume, cover letter, or similar employment-related materials). We use this information for the purpose of processing and responding to your application for current and future career opportunities.
  * If you contact us with a question, comment or complaint, we may collect your name and business contact information (such as your email address or mailing address) in order for us to respond to your request. We may also keep a record of the correspondence in order to assist you in the future.
  * If you post or otherwise provide us with comments, suggestions and other feedback, we may use your comments, suggestions or feedback to monitor and/or improve our products, Services and Website.

**Website Information and Analytics**

In general, you can visit our Website or a Hub we maintain on behalf of one of our Customers (the “Websites”) without indicating who you are or submitting any personal information. However, we collect and/or maintain the IP (Internet protocol) addresses of all visitors to the Websites and other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on the Websites. We use this information to help us understand Website activity and to monitor and improve the Websites.

**Cookies & Similar Technologies:** The Websites use a technology called “cookies”. A cookie is a tiny element of data that the Websites can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so that you can be recognized when you return. We use cookies on the pages on the Websites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable. If you have registered with the Websites, these cookies may let us know who you are and identify your browser as one that has visited the Website before and may be necessary to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver products and personalized services. We also use cookies to provide us and our service providers with information about your use of the Websites that we will use to personalize the Websites or other content in accordance with your interests and preferences (e.g. language or currency preference) and improve your user experience. You may set your Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to not accept certain cookies. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from the Websites, you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features of the Websites. Our Cookie Policy can be found here – https://www.uberflip.com/legal/cookie-policy/

**Tracer Tags & Web Beacons:** The Websites may also use a technology called “tracer tags” or “Web Beacons”. This technology allows us to understand which pages you visit on the Websites. These tracer tags are used to help us optimize and tailor the Websites for you and other future visitors to the Websites.

**Analytics:** We collect information about the Services that you use and how you use them, which may include the pages most read, time spent, zoom pattern, search terms and other engagement data on the Websites. We use this information in order to better understand and improve the Uberflip Website. When you visit one of our Customer’s Hubs, we collect this information on behalf of our Customer and provide our Customer with reports in aggregate form regarding the usage of their Website so that they can better understand the engagement of Audience Members who access and interact with their User Content. We may also combine this information with contact information you input on our Customer’s Hub or Website and provide it to the Customer so that they may better understand your preferences and tailor their communications to you.

We provide analytics to our Customers through our own proprietary dashboards. We may also use a third party such as Google Analytics to help us gather and analyze information about the areas visited on the Websites in order to evaluate and improve the user experience and the convenience of the Websites, and to help us evaluate some of the specific information related to your Website visits. For more information or to opt-out, see [“How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps”](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

**Links:** Our Website may contain links to other websites that we do not own or operate. Also, links to our Website may be featured on third party websites on which we advertise. Except as provided herein, we will not provide any of your personal information to these third parties without your consent. We provide links to third party websites as a convenience to the user. These links are not intended as an endorsement of or referral to the linked websites. The linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies, notices and terms of use, which we recommend you read carefully. We do not have any control over such websites, and therefore we have no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use or disclose, secure and otherwise treat your personal information.

**Online Interest-Based Advertising**

We also work with third-parties such as ad networks and other advertising companies that use their own tracking technologies (including cookies, tracer tags, web beacons and pixel tags) on our Website and other websites in order to provide you with tailored advertisements on our behalf across the Internet (including social media websites and apps). These companies may collect information about your activity across your different devices on our Website and third-party websites (such as web pages you visit and your interaction with our advertising) and use this information to deliver ads that are more relevant and tailored to you on our Website and third party websites.

We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada’s (DAAC) Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. To learn more about this interest-based advertising practice and to understand your options, including how you can opt-out of receiving interest-based ads from participating third-party advertising companies, please visit the Digital Advertising Alliance website at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada website at [www.youradchoices.ca/choices](http://www.youradchoices.ca/choices).

To successfully opt-out, you must have cookies enabled in your web browser. Please see your browser’s instructions for information on cookies and how to enable them. Your opt-out only applies to the web browser you use so you must opt-out of each web browser on each device that you use. Once you opt out, if you delete your browser’s saved cookies, you may need to opt-out again.

Please note that even if you opt-out interest-based advertising by a third party, these tracking technologies may still collect data for other purposes including analytics and you will still see ads from us, but the ads will not be targeted based on behavioral information about you and may therefore be less relevant to you and your interests.

To opt-out of Uberflip specific advertising please visit – https://www.uberflip.com/legal/#cookie-policy

**Social Media**

We may offer Customers or Audience Members with the opportunity to engage with content or Hubs on or through third-party social networking websites, plug-ins and applications. When Audience Members engage with content on or through third-party social networking websites, plug-ins and applications, they may allow us to have access to certain information associated with their social media account (e.g., name, username, email address, profile picture, gender) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the website, plug-in or application. When Audience Members provide information from their social media account, we may use this information to personalize their experience on the Website and on the third-party social networking websites, plug-ins and applications, and to provide other products or services the Audience Member may request.

**Location and Device Information**

If you use a location-enabled service, we may obtain your consent to collect information about your device’s physical location in order to provide you with relevant content and to better understand our Customers and Audience Members. We may collect this information based on IP address or nearby Wifi access points and cell towers. You can change your device settings to allow or block the collection of location information. Please note that if you turn off the collection of location information, we may not be able to provide all services to you.

Transfers and Disclosures of Personal Information

As a matter of practice, Uberflip does not disclose, trade, rent, sell or otherwise transfer our customers’ personal information, except as set out in this Privacy Policy or in the Terms of Use our Customers enter into with Uberflip.

**Hubs:** If you interact with a Hub, we collect information you provide as postings (such as any comments you may post). Please remember that any information that you provide in these comment areas is accessible to the public, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information about yourself or anyone else.

**Service Providers:** In connection with our Website or the Services we provide to our Customers, we may transfer personal information to third-party service providers who provide services on our behalf in Canada, the United States or other jurisdictions. Our service providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize to use or disclose personal information for their own purposes. For example, we may use service providers to host the Website or Hubs, send email or other communications, generate leads, process payments, provide analytics and advertising services, moderate online discussions, and run our contests and surveys. For additional information about the way in which our service providers treat personal information, please contact us as set out in the “Contact Us” section below.

**Sale of Business:** We may disclose or transfer personal information to a third party as an asset in connection with prospective or completed a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of Uberflip, or as part of a corporate reorganization or stock sale or other change in corporate control.

**Legal obligations:** We, our affiliates and our Canadian, U.S. and other service providers may provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, for the purposes of detecting, preventing or suppressing fraud, or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable Canadian, US or other law (which may include lawful access requests by courts, law enforcement and government institutions in such foreign jurisdictions). Where disclosure of our Customer’s information is required by applicable law, we promptly notify our Customer prior to complying with such requirements (to the extent we are not prohibited from doing so).

We may also disclose personal information where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims and to investigate or prevent actual or suspect loss or harm to persons or property.

**Aggregate Data:** We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly or to potential Customers, such as to show trends about the general use and effectiveness of our services.

**Safeguarding**

We understand that data security is a critical issue for our Customers. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect personal information in our custody and under our control against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure.

Your online access to certain of your personal information may be protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication (such as letters, phone calls or email messages).

**Retention**

We have personal information retention processes designed to retain personal information for no longer than necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or provided to us or to otherwise meet legal requirements.

**Accuracy & Access**

If we receive a request from an individual to access or update personal information we maintain on behalf of a Customer, we will direct that individual to the relevant Customer. We will assist our customers wherever possible in responding to individual access requests.

Subject to limited exceptions prescribed by law, you may otherwise request access, updating or correction of your personal information under our control by submitting a written request and satisfactory identification to Uberflip at the contact information set out under Contact Us below.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically to reflect changes to our personal information practices. The revised Privacy Policy will be posted on this Website. We strongly encourage you to please refer to this Privacy Policy often for the latest information about our personal information practices.

**Contact Us**

Please contact Uberflip at [support@uberflip.com](mailto:support@uberflip.com) with any questions or concerns that you may have about this Privacy Policy or the manner in which personal information is collected, used, disclosed and otherwise managed by Uberflip.

## Sub-processors

As part of Uberflip’s ongoing commitment to the privacy and protection of our customers’ personal data, please click here for the lists of sub-processors that we work with currently.
